dashthis.com 2016-12-06

# Our Privacy Policy | DashThis - Analytics, PPC & SEO Reporting

Protecting our customers’ information and privacy is our top priority. DashThis’s privacy policy includes its employees, agents, partners, contractors and affiliates.

We treat information about our customers, including personal information, as strictly confidential, consistent with all legal and regulatory requirements. We employ a combination of technology and standard practices to ensure your information is safeguarded from unauthorized access or exposure. The information we collect about you in the course of conducting normal business will only be shared with third parties upon your consent or as required by law. We collect customer information based on our business relationship with you and your use of the services and solutions we provide. Some examples include:

  * Contact information that allows us to communicate with you, including your name, address, telephone number and email address.
  * Billing information related to your financial relationship with us, including your payment data and history. Our third-party payment provider, Moneris, must receive your payment data in order to process your payment with DashThis. You can view Moneris’ privacy policy here: [Moneris privacy policy](http://www.moneris.com/Privacy%20Policy.aspx)
  * Data in order to connect our dashboard solution to you or your clients’ data sources.

For more information or to address any concerns, please contact [info@dashthis.com](mailto:info@dasthis.com)

## Do you store my passwords?

No. Most data source providers have a secure way of authentication that does not entail providing your credentials. Most of the time, the standardize process oAuth2 (<http://oauth.net/2/>), is used. We only store a secure token that is given by the API provider when you complete the authorization process. This allows us to fetch data and generate your dashboards without having you to perform an authorization every day.

Other data sources will need an API key. This key is sensitive and must be handle like a password. Finally, in few cases, the data source provider will require a username and password. In such cases, it’s a best practice to create an account for this purpose only and not use your DashThis administrator credentials.

## How safe is DashThis?

Internet communications between DashThis and Google Analytics use SSL encrypted HTTPS connections. We know data confidentiality is critical to our clients and their trust in our product is based on our capacity to protect their data. We implement the best security practices in the industry.

## What analytics data do you store?

We store aggregate data of your dashboard in our database. This is for performance purposes only as it would take too much time to get the data from data source APIs to rebuild your dashboards every time you consult them.

Most of the time, data from data source providers is read-only; therefore, there is no way we can add, update or delete it. In the other cases, we might request permission to edit account information; however, we do so only to get analytic information. In no way do we edit, update or delete account information.

## Data property

It’s your data. You own the data. We do not use it for anything else other to display it in your dashboards. Any stored data will be deleted upon a client’s request.

## Who will have access to my data?

You and those to whom you will give access to your dashboards. Dashboards have unique encrypted URLs so that you get fast and safe access without having to log in. This URL is like a password. Be sure to keep it safe.

Our staff might access your data to debug any issues or make minor adjustments to improve performance. DashThis will not reveal your dashboards to anyone under any circumstances.

## What happens when I delete a dashboard?

Everything is deleted. Your configuration as well as any data we would have retrieved and stored.

## This website uses Google AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the DashThis website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. 

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/). 

## Do you have any other concerns or questions?

Contact us and we'll be glad to help!
